<resources>
    <string name="toast_failed_show_ad">To download the mod, first watch the video by clicking on DOWNLOAD!</string>
	<string name="invalid_link">Something went wrong.</string>
	<string name="no_mods">Coming soon.</string>
	<string name="guide_text">Hello! \n\n
        This section does not describe the functions of this application, but describes only instructions on how to install the mod (which you can download in our application) into the Minecraft PE game, which must be installed on your device. \n\n
        The purpose of the instructions is to help you install the mod into the Minecraft PE game, which is a separate application from our application. \n\n
        <b> Instructions for installing mods on MCPE </b> \n
        1. Download the mod file. \n
        You can find information on how to download the mod by clicking on the "INFO" button in the main menu of the application. \n
        2. Find it in the downloads of your device and press. \n
        3. The game will automatically launch and the import process will begin. \n
        3. The game will automatically launch and the import process will begin. \n
        4. Turn on the mod in world editing. \n
        5. Done! \n\n
        <b> Installing mods with the .mcpack extension </b> \n
        1. Download to your device a mod with the extension .mcpack \n
        2. If you already have MCPE installed, then just find the mod file and run it. \n
        3. After clicking, the game will automatically start and import the mod. \n
        4. After successfully importing all parts of the mod, go to editing the world and in the Resource Sets or Parameter Sets section, activate the mod. \n
        5. Activation in Resource Sets or Parameter Sets depends on the type of mod, and there can be several files. \n
        6. If you need to enable experiment functions for the mod to work, then do it. \n
        7. After successful activation, you can start the world and enjoy the installed mod! \n\n
        <b> Installing mods with .mcaddon extension </b> \n
        1. Download to your device a mod with the extension .mcaddon \n
        2. If you already have MCPE installed, then just find the mod and run it. \n
        3. The game will automatically start and import will start. \n
        4. After successfully importing all parts of the mod, go to editing the world and in the Resource Sets and Parameter Sets sections, activate all parts of the mod. \n
        5. If necessary, enable the experiment functions required for the mod to work. \n
        6. Now you can start the world and enjoy the installed add-on! \n</string>
	<string name="info_text_part_one">Hello! \n
        In this application you can download the mod for MCPE to make the game process even more interesting and dynamic. \n\n
        To see all the mods of our development studio, click on the “ALL MODS” button in the main menu.</string>
	<string name="info_text_part_two">To download a mod for MCPE: \n \n
        1. Press the “DOWNLOAD” button in the main menu; \n
        2. Download the mod by clicking on the "DOWNLOAD" button (you will go to the Google Disk, where the mod is stored, for downloading); \n
        3. Install the mod according to the instructions that you will find by pressing the “GUIDE” button in the main menu. \n\n
        Now you can start the world and enjoy the installed add-on!</string>
	<string name="download_text">Hello! \n \n
        In this section, you can download the mod on MCPE, to your device. \n \n
        To download the mod, click on the “DOWNLOAD” button (you will need to watch ads and you will go to the DropBox link where the mod is stored for download). \n \n
        You can view detailed information by clicking on the “GUIDE” button in the main menu of the application.</string>
	<string name="all_mods">Hello! \n \n
        In this section, you will find all the mods of our development studio that you can install for yourself on MCPE. \n \n
        When you click on the icon of any of the mods, you will go to our Play Market to download it. \n \n
        Choose and download!</string>
	<string name="description_of_logo">Logotype "GO Games Studio"</string>
	<string name="description_of_btn_info">Button "Information"</string>
	<string name="description_of_btn_guide">Button "Guide"</string>
	<string name="description_of_btn_download">Button "Download"</string>
	<string name="description_of_btn_video">Button "Screen"</string>
	<string name="description_of_screen">Screen</string>
	<string name="description_of_btn_all_mods">All mods button</string>
	<string name="image_mod_desc">Mod icon</string>
    <string name="no_connection">To download the mod, turn on the Internet connection!</string>
    <string name="file_was_downloaded">File was downloaded</string>
    <string name="open_folder">Open Folder</string>
    <string name="provide_permission">Please grant permission to be able to download file</string>
    <string name="downloading">Downloading</string>
    <string name="error">Error downloading file. Please, try again.</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="watch_ad_reward_confirmation">Do you want to watch ads to get access to download mod files?</string>
</resources>